and what happened to
а что случилось с
him died Well, like a bomb lands, a
ним погиб Ну типа как бомба прилёт
mine, and a scoop lands in the neck, horror, in the
мина а скова прилетела в шею ужас в
carotid artery And that he went to
Сонную артерию А что он пошёл на
war Well, I have a military family Well,
войну ну у меня семья военных Ну
like a military uncle, a military brother, an uncle and an
как дядя военный брат военный дядя и
older brother, too, at war Yes, they haven't gotten it yet
брат старший тоже на войне Да им пока
Hello Hello, let's have a normal
Здравствуй Здраствуй давай нормально
conversation
пообщаемся
I'm not arguing Yes, I'm not arguing
Я не ссорюсь Да я не ссорюсь
Come on, you're so sharp, sporty,
Ну давайте ты такая чёткая спортивная
Adidas Buur, my father is from
Адидасом буур у меня отец из
Sverdlovsk, that's just it Well,
Свердловской родом вот это как раз Ну
when he was still in Sverdlovsk, damn You,
когда он ещё был Свердловском блин Тебе
Heart, heart, he said there, generally,
Сердечко сердечко он говорил там вообще
boys and girls all
пацаны и девчонки все в спортивном
wore sports clothes He says earlier, and what are you talking about?
ходили говорит раньше а чём общаешься
I'm just bored for now I understand How old are
мне пока просто скучно понял Сколько
you
тебе
26 About what do you
лет 26 о Кем
work in a beer store in a beer
работаешь в пивном магазине в пивном
store Is this your
магазине Это твоя
uniform No, this is my uniform at home Are you at
униформа Нет это моя униформа дома Ты
home now Yes, I understand what are you talking about here Well, I'll
сейчас дома да понял о чём тут общаешься
find out about this and that How are you doing Yes, I
Ну так о том о сём узнаю как дела Да что
understand Are you looking for a boyfriend
понял парня ищешь
No, I have a boyfriend  You don't have it
Нет есть парень У тебя
and you don't and you're not looking, that is, you don't
нет так и нет и не ищешь то есть тебе не
need a guy. No, a
нужен парень
feminist.
феминистка
No, I got it. In short, on guys. Yes, I got it.
нет понял просто короче на парней да да
They're some kind of punks there in
понял они там гопники какие-то в этом в
Yekaterinburg now. Yes, that's it. Well, I wouldn't
Екатеринбурге сейчас Да все Да ну не
say that
сказать что
punks drink. In short, there aren't any normal
гопники бухают Да короче нет нормального
men anymore. There are only
мужика уже да одни
Tajiks. There are a lot of Tajiks. Dan, I have
таджики таджиков много
acquaintances who are at
Даня знакомые есть которые на
war. Is there someone who is my
войне есть есть кто-то кто
own brother? My own. My God, what happened
родной Трою Родный Боже а что случилось
to
с
him? Like a bomb, a
ним ну типа как бомба прилёт
mine, and a scoop hits my neck, in the carotid
мина а скова прилетела в шею в Сонную
artery. And that he went to
артерию А что он пошёл на
war. Well, I have a military family. Well,
войну ну у меня семья военных Ну
like my uncle is a military man. My older brother is a military man.
как дядя военный брат военный старший и
He also went. My uncle and older brother are also
он тоже пошёл дядя и брат старший тоже
at war. Yes, they haven't gotten it yet.
на войне Да им пока ещё не
No, how much was paid for this one
нет А сколько выплатили за этого
who
которому
got it. I don't know. I didn't even ask. I don't know.
прилетело я не знаю я не стала даже
Well, how much do they pay
зна Ну а сколько приблизительно платят
for it in Russia, approximately.
за это в России
Well, about 2 Milonov. Well, maybe even
Ну около 2 Милонов Ну может даже типа
more. I don't know. I'm not getting involved. And what did
больше я не знаю я не втягиваю и Что
Mom buy
Мамка купила
it for? I don't know. I don't recognize. I got it.  And so are there
его я не знаю я не узнаю понял А так ещё
any other acquaintances wounded dead
какие-то знакомые раненые погибшие есть
No
Нет
no And why did they go to kill
нету А зачем они вообще пошли убивать
people in another
людей в другую
country Let's say I can ask the same
страну Допустим я могу задать тот же
question ask
вопрос задай
why did you start a war with us I mean
зачем вы начали войну с нами в смысле
it was you who started it with us you attacked
это вы начали с нами вы напали на
Ukraine have you become so
Украину вы что вообще
brazen no Well tell me how Ukraine
обнаглели нет А ну расскажи как Украина
attacked Russia well as far as I remember in
напала на Россию ну насколько я помню в
1914 when the war started in
четырнадцатом году когда началась война
1914 When the war started the
четырнадцатом Когда началась война
Ukrainians fled we had
украинцы бежали у нас были
refugees Ukraine attacked
беженцы Украина нападала на
Russia no no well that means you attacked Ukraine
Россию нет нет ну так значит вы напали
your troops came to Ukraine
на Украину ваши войска в Украину пришли
we on the contrary helped there I don't even
мы наоборот помогали там я даже не
get into it In short I don't get into it all in short
вникаю Короче я не вникаю во всё короче
how did you help bomb cities bombing
как помогли разбомбили города бомбить
kill what are you
убиваете что же вы
helping
помогаете
listen I don't kill I don't get involved in
послушайте я не убиваю я не лезу в это
all this If I went like that I would go I have a
всё Если бы я пошла так Я бы пошла У
son growing up I have a child growing up from
меня растёт сын у меня растёт ребёнок от
whom I don't need this from whom is the son I
кого мне это не надо от кого сын у меня
have a son can you imagine from whom From the husband
есть сын представляете От кого От мужа А
Where is the husband
где
we got divorced Yeah he's at
муж мы развелись Ага он на
war
войне
no He
нет
drank  and drank and drank understood in short according to Russian
Пил и пил и пил понял короче по русской
tradition and drinks or drinks not always but
традиции и пьёт или пьёт не не всегда но
there is such a thing
есть такое
understood And what do you think why Russia
понял А как ты считаешь вот зачем Россия
attacked Ukraine at all
вообще напала на
I won't even tell you just your
Украину я даже Вам не скажу просто твоя
thought here I am a simple person and also
мысль вот я простой человек и тоже с
communicate with simple people Here I am
простыми людьми общаюсь Вот мне
interested in what they think
интересно как они думают
as far as I know that we, on the contrary,
насколько я знаю то что мы наоборот
helped Ukrainians because in
помогали потому что украинцев в
1914 when refugees came
четырнадцатом году когда беженцы пришли
to us here to us here we
к нам вот к нам вот у нас вот беженцы
had refugees in 1914 Here they are with us here we
были в четырнадцатом году Вот они у нас
still have them So it was in
вот они у нас всё ещё есть Так это же в
1914 yes Russia attacked
четырнадцатом году да Россия напала на
Ukraine Crimea Donetsk Lugansk and
Украину Крым Донецк Луганск и побежали
refugees ran because there was a war well then
беженцы потому что война была ну ту
refugees ran to us they ran to us and
беженцы же побежали к нам они и к нам и
to you They are where the war is going on
к вам побежали Они вот Где идёт Война
they are running in all directions refugees where
они во все стороны бегут беженцы куда
can you run away from the war
можно убежать от войны
where do you have any relatives
где родственники какие-то
we don't even have relatives here
есть у нас даже тут родственников и не
Although they ran straight
было Хотя они побежали вот прямо вообще
straight Russia
прям Россия
visit I have
посети У меня кстати
this too by the way  there was an acquaintance in short from Russia
этот тоже был знакомый короче из России
You are from Yekaterinburg And he is from Saratov
Вот ты из Екатеринбурга А он из Саратова
Sanya Prokhorov We once met
Саня Прохоров мы когда-то познакомились
at sea in Turkey
на море Турции
in short this started his own thing he also went
короче он вот это началось сво пошл тоже
to his own place so that like refugees something also told me something like that
на сво чтоб типа беженцы что-то тоже мне
died you know
такое погиб знаешь
how a very terrible
как очень страшной
death there they had this well trenches and in the
смертью там был у них этот ну окопы и в
trenches Well you are not in the trench because
окопах Ну ты же не в окопе потому что
there it is the Armed Forces It stinks they had
там оно ВС Воняет у них так в конце
such a special
окопа был такой специальный
toilet at the end of the trench yamas Well b
туалет ямас
dugout Well in short here is a dugout - This is a
Ну б блиндаж Ну короче вот блиндаж - Это
trench from a dugout and at the end of the trench there is
от блиндажа окоп и в конце окопа там
such a hole and they went there for a month with
такая дырка и они вот это месяц туда
this whole platoon did he go
всем этим взводом ходили ли он пошёл
there and they tracked him down with a drone Yes and he
туда а его выследили с дрона Да и
flew to him he was sitting with his
прилетел ему он сидел со спущенными
pants down Well to empty himself and the drone
штанами Ну опорожняться и Дрон ему
flew to him right yes And this is what the Ukrainians
прилетел прямо да И вот это украинцы
showed our Here is this video uh
показывали наше Вот это видео ээ
in short he sits flies in The drone flies off
короче он сидит прилетает Дрон отлетает
like a football Yes and the body is still sitting
как футбольный мяч Да а тело ещё сидит
In short the body is still sitting like it turns out well ti
Короче тело ещё сидит типа получается ну
and the body well and then in this  a hole like
ти а тело ну и потом в эту яму типа
collapsed it was horror it's like a
провалилось это было ужа это Это как
chicken And a head yes what a chicken they
курица Да и голову да что курица голову
wipe its head it runs and this is Sanya prokhorov he's
отрут она бегает а это Саня прохо он
still it's just the Ukrainians made such a
ещ это просто же украинцы сделали такой
video like yes like it's called
видеоролик типа да типа называется
this and they
этот так и
called it the Ukrainians made Yes
назвали украинцы сделали Да
shaley I sent it to my mom I also say
шалей я его маме присылал ещё говорю
Look Sanka
Смотри Санька
relaxed there yes it's funny and not funny
расслабился там да и смешно и не смешно
funny damn really the occupier
смешно блин реально оккупант
in short fell
короче упал
Yes Listen and what do you think like why are
Да Слушай а как ты считаешь типа зачем
all these Russians
все эти русские
dying they are dying not for their own That's for sure Yes
гибнут они гибнут не за своё Это точно
so I'm dying for Putin Putin for himself in short
Да так за Путина гибну Путин себе короче
all these sons of all sorts of
его вот эти все сыночки всяких типа
officials they hang out Yes girls in bars
чиновников они себе тусят Да в барах
and simple ones like Sanya Prokhorov
девочки а простых вот как Саня Прохоров
should die somewhere in nameless ravines
должны где-то безымянных оврагах
Yes everyone talks about this there's
умирать Да все об этом говорят
no sense in this And what do you people say
никакого А что у вас люди говорят
in general I wish it would all end soon that's
вообще скоре бы уже это всё закончилось
what they say there is hope for Trump
вот что они говорят надежда на трампа
yes probably
есть да наверное
now I have no hope at all for him
сейчас у меня вот вообще на не на него
I don't
надежды никакой нету Я вот вообще я не
get into this at all I buy  she is not needed I do
лезу в это поку Мне она не нужна Я
n't even look at it Because
вообще даже не смотрю на это Потому что
when I thought that I would collect my
когда я думала то что у меня соберёт
moons I was very worried about the
муны сво Я очень сильно переживала
child being small But you are
ребёнок маленький Так ты же
divorced Well before that the war
разведена Ну так до этого война то
started 2 years ago and according to the
началась 2 года назад а по
po Well not two already 3 years ago already the
по Ну уже не два уже 3 года назад уже
fourth has
четвёртый
gone the third already the fourth has gone three
пошёл третий уже четвёртый пошёл три
full years have passed the
полных
third has gone Well look it
прошло третий пошёл Ну смотри оно
started in February 20 the second now it's already the
началось в феврале 20 второго сейчас уже
twenty-fifth year 2 p
двадцать пятый год 2 п
March
март
yes three full years was
да три полных года было 24
February 24 And now what do you think If they
февраля А сейчас как считаешь Если мужа
take away my husband is it good or
заберут хорошо или
bad bad And what can you
плохо плохо А что бабки можешь
make of the money I know That's what I need It would be
срубить Я знаю Вот они вот мне нужны Вот
better for me to have it with a child than for me to have
лучше бы у меня будет с ребёнком чем мне
these Well he's busy with the
вот эти А ну он занимается типа с
child like Yes Like he is yes He takes him away
ребёнком Да Типа он да Он забирает его
yes And that's it Well then I thought he just
да А всё Ну тогда я думал просто он
drinks no
пьёт нет
but he just doesn't need to drink Yeah It's the
а ему просто пить не надо
same for everyone and you he works as
Угу Это у всех и у вас также он работат
what he
кем он
works as a bulldozer driver a bulldozer driver and it
работает бульдозерист бульдозерист а ему
seems to him somewhere there is a head  bulldozers he
походу где-то там башку бульдозерами он
yes
да
No I understand how you think that's also an
Нет понял как считаешь вот тоже
interesting question Why does Russia have
интересный вопрос Почему в России есть
oil gas gold diamonds the richest
нефть газ золото алмазы богатейшая
country Yes and people live so
страна Да а живут люди так
poorly I also
бедно Я тоже таким же вопросом
ask myself the same question Where does this money go
задаюсь Куда эти деньги деваются
everyone all rich scam all rich
все всё богатенькие скам всё богатенький
people And why yours Here these poor people are
людям А почему ваши Вот Эти бедные люди
all silent And silently go to die for these
все молчат И молча идут умирать за этих
rich Russian
богатеньких российских
people Yes you Why are you asking me
людей Да вы Почему у меня-то спрашиваете
How do I know Ask Well you poor
Я откуда знаю Спросите Ну бы вы бедные
poor people that's what they
бедный люди вот у вас и
ask you I'm not a poor person Well an ordinary
спрашивают я не бедный людь Ну обычный
poor person You're not a rich man this is not an
бедный людь Вы же не богач не это
oligarch who takes all this oil
олигарх который эти всю нефть забирает
True Well I don't have that but I don't
Правда Ну у меня нету такого но я не
consider myself
считаю себя
poor you have a car no
бедным машина у вас
But I have a
есть нету Зато у меня есть квартира
large two-room apartment well you
двухкомнатная большая
see that is The point is that
ну вот видите то есть Суть в том что а у
Putin Medvedev there Peskova
Путина Медведева там Пескова у ихних
all their kids So
всех деточек
what now
есть Ну и что теперь
nothing to start Why don't you have well
не нечего начинать Почему у вас нет ну
because my time hasn't
потому что у меня ещё время ещё не
come yet I'll earn as soon as I earn  will understand
пришло Я как заработаю так и будет понял
child boy boy
ребёнок
How old already
мальчик мальчик Сколько лет уже
3 years in 15 years will you give him to
3 года через 15 лет отдашь его на
some
какую-то
war No I don't want I won't give him Not for Well the
войну Нет не хочу Не отдам Не за Ну
state will take him Yes
заберёт государство Да
now And what do your parents think about
сейчас А что твои родители думают про
this
эту
war and
войну и
my parents my parents are also against this
родители мои родители тоже против этой
war no one needs it now the 10th century
войны никому Она не нужна сейчас X век
who needs it no one needs it even
кому она нужна никому Она не нужна даже
you don't need it Well for some reason a bunch of
и вам она не нужна Ну почему-то куча
Russia we need it they go to
Россия она нам нужна они идут
war Well they are not fighting of their
воюют Ну они же воюют не по своей
own free will They sign
собственной воле По своей подписывают
contracts of their own free will these are
контракты ба по свое вот это вот
contract soldiers yes they go for the sake of and that's it
контрактники да они идут ради и
Let's
всё Давайте
conclude Everything I don't want I No everything let's
заключим Всё я не хочу я Нет всё давайте
communicate normally not
нормально нормально общаемся не
normally we communicate It's very nice to
нормально общаемся Это очень приятно
meet a person who is not drunk here
встретить человека который не пьяный тут
yes And normally Maybe we should talk you
да А нормально Может поговорить мы
see Ukrainians should
видите украинцы с россиянами должны
try to communicate with Russians and think what do we
пробовать общаться и думать что же мы
think No that's clear Yes I understand everything
думаем Нет это понятно Да Я всё понимаю
but for me It's a difficult topic
но для меня Тяжёлая тема
why Well because I lost my brother
почему Ну потому что я брата потеряла
imagine for me so he is a second cousin
представляете для меня так он троюродный
so he is a
так он
second cousin So what he is closer to me than my
троюродный Ну и что он для меня роднее
own And his mother is also
родного А мама его также
worried about him Let's not do everything  okay let's
переживает Давайте не будем всё ладно
let's let's pray for my
давайте давай Давайте Помолимся за
brother broke down Now we would pray for
брата сорвалась Сейчас бы помолились
glass wool for my
ля стекловата для
brother a letter on Telegram right now axis
брата пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN a
ВН а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube is
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy with us through scarg ORV in your ban and
заня нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и
very many videos I don't show people
дуже багато видео не показую людям
at times I don't show information about streams so
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
that we Mali operational
тому для того чтоб мы Мали оперативный
links are written right now And
звязок пишиться прямо зараз А по
there in Telegram we will find videos that are also
там в телеграми окрим видео ще теж
interesting and useful information and we will answer
цикава и корисна информация и мы повинни
you for the constant operational
з вами тримати постийний оперативный
links
звязок
independently in that che will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine a
YouTube Слава Украине
letter a
пись а